[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1994 Woody Allen movie stars Dianne Wiest as an alcoholic actress and John Cusack as the neurotic persona?", "correct_answer": "Bullets Over Broadway", "incorrect_answers": ["Everyone Says I Love You", "Celebrity", "Melinda and Melinda"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This volcano, which is the largest in Europe, is located on the largest island in the Mediterranean Sea.", "correct_answer": "Mount Etna", "incorrect_answers": ["Hekla", "El Misti", "Santorini"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you were born in 1980, 1992 or 2004, what would your lunar sign be?", "correct_answer": "monkey", "incorrect_answers": ["ox", "dog", "ram"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the executive chef of the kitchen called?", "correct_answer": "Chef de Cuisine", "incorrect_answers": ["Saut\u00e9 Chef", "Chef de Partie", "Sous Chef"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Niacin, also known as vitamin B3 or nicotinic acid, is a vitamin that can be synthesized by which organ?", "correct_answer": "Liver", "incorrect_answers": ["Heart", "Kidneys", "Gall-bladder"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Michael Mann movie was adapted from the Vanity Fair article The Man Who Knew Too Much by Marie Brenner.", "correct_answer": "The Insider", "incorrect_answers": ["Frailty", "Eyes Wide Shut", "The Hurricane"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the holy river of the Hindu people?", "correct_answer": "The Ganges", "incorrect_answers": ["The Euphrates", "The Indus", "The Tigris"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What group of dogs does the beagle belong to?", "correct_answer": "hound", "incorrect_answers": ["retrievers", "setters", "terriers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animal is responsible for the most human deaths in the world?", "correct_answer": "Mosquito", "incorrect_answers": ["Great White Shark", "Pitbull", "Wasp"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1951 film did Humphrey Bogart win an Oscar for?", "correct_answer": "African Queen", "incorrect_answers": ["The Barefoot Contessa", "The Caine Mutiny", "Casablanca"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of Scouts family in the 1962 classic To Kill a Mockingbird?", "correct_answer": "Finch", "incorrect_answers": ["McKinney", "Mannete", "Oswald"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Church of the Holy Sepulchre, also called the Church of the Resurrection, is an example of Byzantine architecture, located in which city?", "correct_answer": "Jerusalem, Israel", "incorrect_answers": ["Moscow, Russia", "Rome, Italy", "Istanbul, Turkey"]}]